<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<source>
  <job>
    <title>Security Officer – Long Beach</title>
    <date>2025-10-02</date>
    <company>Orchid Protection Services</company>
    <location>Long Beach, CA</location>
    <description><![CDATA[
      Orchid Protection Services is hiring professional Security Officers to serve Long Beach communities with integrity and care. We value reliability, empathy, and a commitment to safety. Roles include foot patrol, access control, and incident reporting. Inclusive teams. Paid training. Uniform provided.
    ]]></description>
    <url>https://www.orchidprotectionservices.com/join-us</url>
  </job>

  <job>
    <title>Security Officer – Los Angeles County</title>
    <date>2025-10-02</date>
    <company>Orchid Protection Services</company>
    <location>Los Angeles County, CA</location>
    <description><![CDATA[
      Join our LA County team of Security Officers protecting diverse communities across the region. Orchid Protection Services offers structured shifts, branded support systems, and a culture of respect. Duties include site monitoring, client interaction, and safety documentation.
    ]]></description>
    <url>https://www.orchidprotectionservices.com/join-us</url>
  </job>

  <job>
    <title>Security Officer – Riverside</title>
    <date>2025-10-02</date>
    <company>Orchid Protection Services</company>
    <location>Riverside, CA</location>
    <description><![CDATA[
      Orchid Protection Services is seeking Security Officers for Riverside sites. Ideal candidates are dependable, observant, and community-minded. Responsibilities include perimeter checks, visitor screening, and incident escalation. Branded onboarding and regional support included.
    ]]></description>
    <url>https://www.orchidprotectionservices.com/join-us</url>
  </job>

  <job>
    <title>Security Officer – San Bernardino</title>
    <date>2025-10-02</date>
    <company>Orchid Protection Services</company>
    <location>San Bernardino, CA</location>
    <description><![CDATA[
      Serve San Bernardino neighborhoods with Orchid Protection Services. We’re hiring Security Officers who bring professionalism and calm to dynamic environments. Roles include patrol, access control, and client coordination. Inclusive culture. Paid training. Branded SOPs.
    ]]></description>
    <url>https://www.orchidprotectionservices.com/join-us</url>
  </job>

  <job>
    <title>Security Officer – Orange County</title>
    <date>2025-10-02</date>
    <company>Orchid Protection Services</company>
    <location>Orange County, CA</location>
    <description><![CDATA[
      Orchid Protection Services is expanding in Orange County. We’re hiring Security Officers who value consistency, clarity, and community impact. Duties include site patrol, report writing, and client engagement. Branded systems. Regional support. Inclusive onboarding.
    ]]></description>
    <url>https://www.orchidprotectionservices.com/join-us</url>
  </job>

  <job>
    <title>Security Officer – San Diego</title>
    <date>2025-10-02</date>
    <company>Orchid Protection Services</company>
    <location>San Diego, CA</location>
    <description><![CDATA[
      Join our San Diego team of Security Officers at Orchid Protection Services. We offer structured roles, branded training, and regional support. Responsibilities include patrol, access control, and incident documentation. Inclusive teams. Paid onboarding. Uniform provided.
    ]]></description>
    <url>https://www.orchidprotectionservices.com/join-us</url>
  </job>
</source>